Rabindra Khadka

Mobile: +977 9861354328

Email: rabindrakhadka507@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/rabindra-khadka-581165170

Professional Summary

Network Security Administrator with extensive experience in managing and optimizing network infrastructure in the MSP & ISP sectors. Proficient in troubleshooting, network and System Security, routing, switching, LAN/WAN configurations, system and server management. Holds a B.Sc. in Computer Networking and IT Security from London Metropolitan University and possesses strong analytical and problem-solving skills.

Work Experience

Network Security Administrator

Max International, Kamladi, Kathmandu, Nepal Dec 2021 – August 2024

- Managed and maintained network infrastructure, including routers, switches, servers, and firewalls, ensuring optimal performance and security.
- Deploy and Migrate Next-Gen Firewalls, Network Monitoring tools and Application Performance Monitoring Software, Endpoint Security, MFA, System and Server.
- Enhanced network design for scalability and efficiency through proactive monitoring and troubleshooting.
- Provided technical support and training sessions, resolving network issues and conducting training sessions.
- Developed and maintained comprehensive documentation for security posture management, security checkup, policies tuning, and procedures.

NOC Engineer Interns

Dish Media Network Ltd., Chyasikot-25, Bhaisepati, Lalitpur, Nepal Aug 2021 – Nov 2021

- Resolved customer network issues, collaborating closely with Customer Support Representatives.
- Monitored network performance using Libre NMS and configured network devices (ONTs, OLTs, switches, routers).
- Implemented network security measures, including firewalls, to protect data integrity.
- Delivered corporate support through on-site troubleshooting and technical assistance.
- Compiled detailed reports on device performance and technological comparisons post-evaluation.

Education

B.Sc. (Hons) Computer Networking & IT Security

London Metropolitan University (Islington College), 2019 - 2022 Upper Class Honors

Certifications

- Palo Alto Certified Network Security Engineer (PCNSE)
- Fortinet Certified Professional (FCP)
- Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)
- Checkpoint Quantum Hyperscale Technical Specialist
- RSA ID Plus Certified Administrator
- Checkpoint Harmony Endpoint & Browse Technical Specialist
- Ethical Hacking CompTIA Certified
- Huawei HCI Datacom